Java EE server and you get your
Java EE服务器，您将获得
productions guys and say well now I want
制作人，现在我要说好
to run this Java EE application server
运行此Java EE应用程序服务器
what is that well no it's similar to
那是什么好，不，它类似于
Java isn't it you know he starts the
Java不是吗，您知道他开始了
Java VM but has an application on top of
Java VM，但在之上具有一个应用程序
it well okay so see mr. Java I know how
很好，所以见先生。我知道Java
to start how no I'll just stop I don't
开始不，我就停止，我不
have to do backup I can do this that's
必须做备份，我可以做到这一点
fine then you say well you know what I
好的，然后你说好，你知道我在做什么
have this application here
在这里有这个应用程序
PHP aren't you are you working PHP yeah
PHP是不是您正在使用PHP是的
so now I have this application here PHP
所以现在我在这里有这个应用程序PHP
well PHP how to do this well PHP is
好的PHP如何做到这一点好的PHP是
Apache right just run an Apache oh I
Apache就可以运行Apache哦，我
know how to do Apache I can do that okay
知道怎么做Apache我可以做到的
good
好
so then Ian Shasta right there he says
因此，伊恩·沙斯塔（Ian Shasta）就在他说
well we know guys you really should use
好吧，我们知道您确实应该使用这些人
this this red mine issue tracker system
这个红色矿山问题追踪系统
is pretty good is reading Ruby so you go
读Ruby很不错，所以你去
to the production guys well I'm just
对生产人员来说，我只是
going to use the Ruby application oh no
要使用Ruby应用程序哦，不
stop of that you know I had to learn
你知道我必须学习
Java I had to learn Java EE I had to
Java我必须学习Java EE
learn Apache and PHP I'm not doing Ruby
学习Apache和PHP我不做Ruby
no no no no no I'm not doing Ruby here
不，不，不，不，我不在这里做Ruby
right
对
you know I will stop now this nonsense
你知道我现在就废话了
you developers you're crazy you're my
您的开发人员，您疯了，您是我的
worst enemy you keep changing things all
最糟糕的敌人，你一直在改变一切
the time I'm just getting out now we're
我刚出去的时候我们
going to define here in this company we
要在这家公司定义我们
only going to use you know unless your
只会用你知道的，除非你的
application server running Java 1.2
运行Java 1.2的应用程序服务器
right and that's it no more things and
对，就是没有更多的东西了
then you got stuck you can't do anything
那你就被卡住了
else because now you piss it off your
否则，因为现在你生气了
production guys because they they're not
生产人员，因为他们不是
supposed to keep up with all these right
应该跟上所有这些权利
you know it's very manual process it's
你知道这是非常手工的过程
very you know it's very time consuming
你知道这很耗时
to keep all those stuff running
保持所有这些东西运行
everything so what's the solution to
一切，那么解决方案是什么
this containers right so what you do you
这个容器对，所以你做什么
get your job application put inside a
将您的工作申请书放入
container you get your Java EE
容器即可获取Java EE
application you put inside the container
您放入容器中的应用程序
you get your PHP application put inside
您将您的PHP应用程序放入其中
the container you get your Ruby
你得到Ruby的容器
application put inside the container you
将应用程序放入容器中
get your C handcrafted application put
放置您的C手工应用程序
inside the container right you get the
里面的容器，你得到
craziness state yein is doing this mash
疯狂国家yein正在做这个混蛋
horn and JavaScript and you mix all of
喇叭和JavaScript，然后将所有
that you put inside the container right
你放到容器里面的权利
have you ever tried to stall node right
您是否曾经尝试过使节点停止运行
like
喜欢
a lot of things right so you you put all
很多事情都对了，所以你把所有
of this stuff inside a container and you
这些东西放在一个容器里，你
give the production guy a container
给生产人员一个容器
right so what does he do he gets your
是的，所以他会做什么？
Java container put he knows how to run
他知道如何运行Java容器
how'd you start how to stop how to move
你如何开始如何停止如何移动
your container around he knows how to
你周围的容器他知道如何
back up your container he knows how to
备份您的容器，他知道如何
put load balance your container he knows
使负载平衡您知道的集装箱
how to get your container from your your
如何从您的容器中取出容器
laptop move your test server from a test
便携式计算机将您的测试服务器从测试中移出
server to your production server from a
服务器从生产服务器到生产服务器
production server to your cloud provider
生产服务器到您的云提供商
or you want to running more than one
或者您想运行多个
cloud provider let's put my containing
云提供商，让我把
multiple cloud providers you see them
您看到他们的多个云提供商
going up this Brian
去这个布莱恩
multiple cloud providers right here I'm
多个云提供商，我在这里
going to this right ok so yes he needs
去这个右边好吧，是的，他需要
to prepare this part right here yeah he
在这里准备这部分是的，他
had no idea what I'm going to talk about
不知道我要说什么
now he knows ok so you know so now you
现在他知道了，所以你知道了，现在你
can get all of these come here you can
可以把所有这些都拿到这里
you can have your container you can have
你可以有你的容器
your application and you can really
您的应用程序，您可以真正
streamline the whole process of getting
简化获取的全过程
application running on multiple places
在多个地方运行的应用程序
right and your production guys they know
是的，他们认识的生产人员
how to do all these because containers
如何做所有这些，因为容器
are standardized the biggest revolution
标准化最大的革命
of containers exists for a long time
的容器存在很长时间
I think the first containers are seven
我认为第一个容器是七个
1970s right to make this for a long time
1970年代的权利
but only recently that we agreed on this
但直到最近我们才同意
size of the box right we've all been
盒子的大小，我们都
doing containers but like some of some
做容器，但像一些
more Tupperware containers some were
更多的特百惠容器
like really big wood boxes we didn't
就像我们没有的大木头盒子
have a standard to it now everyone in
现在有一个标准
the industry has agreed to use docker
行业已经同意使用docker
as the packaging right so now we know
作为包装，所以现在我们知道
the size of the box and so now we all
盒子的大小，所以现在我们都
understand not only the sizes this size
不仅了解这个尺寸的尺寸
how the hooks get to it I know how how
钩子如何到达我知道如何
they fit together on top of the other so
它们相互配合在一起，所以
if we agree to this with darker and so
如果我们更深地同意这一点，那么
now we can finally start doing the same
现在我们终于可以开始做同样的事情
thing that happened of the second world
第二世界发生的事情
war uh when the first ships with
当第一个与
containers started they would run you
容器启动，它们会运行你
know a few hundred containers
知道几百个容器
today the big the big container ships
今天大集装箱船
they carry ten thousand containers
他们载着一万个集装箱
fifteen thousand containers right and
一万五千个集装箱
you know they grew a lot during those
你知道他们在那期间成长了很多
years same thing that's going on right
几年同一件事一直在进行
now the the first container platforms
现在是第一个集装箱平台
just out you know Amazon container
刚知道你知道亚马逊的容器
service about a year old Google
服务大约一年的Google
container service about a year old
大约一年的集装箱服务
Microsoft's container service even less
微软的容器服务甚至更少
than that like two months old you know
比大概两个月大
Oracle has just acquired several
甲骨文刚刚收购了几家
container companies right so they're all
集装箱公司对，所以他们都是
just starting to run containers that
刚开始运行容器
means if you right now so containers
意味着如果你现在就这样容器
will be a revolution on how we develop
将是我们发展方式的一场革命
and ship software will completely change
船用软件将完全改变
a lot of things we're talking about so
我们在谈论很多事情
we're talking about micro services
我们正在谈论微服务
you're talking about Java EE you're
您在谈论Java EE
talking about other stuff all of these
谈论其他所有这些
will completely change the way we
将会彻底改变我们的方式
develop software because we're running
开发软件，因为我们正在运行
top of containers so and if you're ready
如果您准备好了，那么容器的顶部
right now if you understand right now
如果你现在就明白
how to use containers then you are ahead
如何使用容器，那么您就领先
of the pack right you're going to be
正确的包装
prepared for this future that's going to
为这个未来做好准备
be this year right I mean I mean saying
是今年，我是说
that for the last year I've been saying
去年我一直在说
the next couple of years so do you very
接下来的几年，你也是如此
halfway through it right
在它的一半
so through this year we're going to have
所以到今年，我们将拥有
a bit more and more things going to be
将会有越来越多的事情发生
shipped using containers so it's
使用容器运输，因此
extremely poor that we do this and so
我们这样做非常可怜
I'm going to show you other bits how
我将向您展示其他方式
many of you guys here are running Java
你们这里很多人都在运行Java
EE here how many of you know how to run
EE这里有多少人知道如何运行
java application alright most people
大多数人都可以使用Java应用程序
okay so we're going to show you how how
好吧，我们将向您展示如何
you can run containers using Java EE and
您可以使用Java EE和
but that's true for anything you're
但这对你来说是真的
doing right now and so you can you can
现在就做，所以你可以
that's that can jump start your process
那可以快速启动您的流程
but but the truth is containers is the
但事实是容器是
right abstraction between developers and
开发人员与
operations right so if you're doing
操作正确，所以如果您在做
containers there's no reason that
容器没有理由
developers are the operations biggest
开发人员是最大的业务
enemy right there's no reason for that
敌人，没有理由
because now we have a clear interface we
因为现在我们有一个清晰的界面
can pack our stuff into containers so we
可以将我们的东西包装到容器中，所以我们
can innovate as much as we want and we
可以根据自己的意愿进行创新，我们
just delivered you to get to production
刚送你去生产
guys the container
伙计们
the issue is what happens if you show up
问题是如果出现
with a big container like you know this
像你这样的大容器
how long do those thing like 30-foot
那些30英尺的东西要持续多久
right there very long right you know if
就在那里很长的时间，你知道如果
you if you show up with one of those
你，如果你出现与那些之一
huge metal containers on port that has
港口的巨大金属容器
no container cranes what do you do with
没有集装箱起重机，您该怎么办
it right it goes crazy right you know
它会变得疯狂吧，你知道
are gonna carry this whole thing are you
会带着这整个东西吗
gonna just shove it inside a bar ship
只是把它推到一艘船上
that's not prepared for it that is the
没有为此做好准备的是
biggest problem you know it doesn't
你知道不是的最大问题
matter it doesn't matter if you
不管你是否重要
developer you're using containers and
使用容器的开发人员
you're kind of packing yourself in
你有点收拾自己
containers if your production guys if
容器，如果您的生产人员
they don't have the tools to run the
他们没有工具来运行
containers what are you going to say I'm
容器你要怎么说我
not going to run this stuff here right I
我不会在这里运行这些东西
have no idea how to run this thing I
我不知道该怎么办
have no idea how to manage the thing oh
不知道该怎么办哦
you mean you mean it instead of one
你的意思是你是说它而不是一个
server I'm going to have dozens of
服务器，我将要拥有数十个
servers I can do this
服务器我可以做到这一点
right so this whole process going on
对，所以整个过程正在进行
right now just hold the tools the we
现在，只要握住我们的工具
call the orchestration tools you know
调用您知道的编排工具
all the orchestration tools are coming
所有的编排工具都来了
on right now so that's the thing so in
现在就这样
terms of Java EE I'm going to go really
Java EE的条款，我真的要去
quick here on this on this discussion
在此快速讨论
but if you come to this URL here jav MN
但是，如果您在此处访问此URL，请访问：
it slash doctor-doctor je there is a
斜线医生je有一个
article that goes into very in a lot of
涉及很多的文章
details and you can actually run all of
详细信息，您实际上可以运行所有
these on your computer so everything I
这些在您的计算机上，所以我
can do here is it just requires you
可以在这里做，只是需要你
three four commands and you can run all
三个四个命令，就可以全部运行
of these here in uh in your computer
这些在你的电脑里
yourself right so let's just gonna take
自己是对的，所以让我们来
a look here how we can do this things
在这里看看我们如何做到这一点
right so we all know we talked a little
对，所以我们都知道我们聊了一点
bit about containers we all know that
关于容器的一点我们都知道
Java EE is a server that has a notion of
Java EE是具有以下概念的服务器：
containers right you know you have a lot
容器，你知道你有很多
of contains the web containers ajb
包含网络容器ajb
containers and basically what we use
容器，基本上是我们使用的
this for is that once you package our
这是因为一旦您打包我们的
application a special way it can run
应用程序可以运行的特殊方式
image for application servers right oh I
应用服务器的映像，对，我
like to say one thing here here Brian's
我想在这里说一件事布莱恩的
going to remember that you know
要记住你知道
JQ e e I'm an old guy right so I kind of
JQ ee我是个老头，所以我有点
you know if I put this here on on Oracle
你知道我是否把这个放在Oracle上
they's gonna say there's not but not not
他们会说没有但没有
j2ee anymore it's Java EE now right the
j2ee了，现在是Java EE
thing is everyone has to me did Oracle
事情是每个人对我来说都做了甲骨文
do good things for Java and the answer
为Java做有益的事情和答案
is yes
是是的
Oracle did amazing things for Java open
甲骨文在Java开放方面做得很棒
JDK is much better now than wasn't then
JDK现在比以前要好得多
it was in Suns time the Java community
在Java社区是Suns时代
has a lot of very cool things that
有很多很酷的东西
didn't exist on Suns time so Oracle puts
在Sun时代不存在，因此Oracle提出
more people to solve security things put
更多人解决安全问题
more people to develop a Java so Java is
更多的人来开发Java，所以Java是
a lot better than he was on Suns time
比他在太阳时代要好得多
right in a lot of ways in one way it's
在很多方面以一种方式
not so this was the diagram that Sun had
并非如此，这是Sun拥有的图表
about Java EE this is the diagram the
关于Java EE，这是图表
Oracle has about Java EE pretty boring
甲骨文对Java EE感到无聊
isn't it I mean like yeah he's like
是不是我是说像是
that's okay right he's been Oracle for
没关系，他曾担任Oracle
five years no you you look at that's
五年不，你看着那是
fine right you know I kind of prefer the
好的，你知道我有点喜欢
fun one right this much better is more
一个更好的乐趣是更多
colorful Milovan come on so I keep I
多彩的米洛万来吧，所以我保持我
keep serious with j2ee if you see
认真对待j2ee
nothing changing it's just the callers
没什么改变，只是呼叫者
right and the database not looks like
正确，数据库看起来不像
Oracle Beauty all right okay so so the
Oracle Beauty很好，所以这样
hell out this containers here and
放开这个容器，
because you put applications how to
因为您将应用程序放在
contain you have a special way to
包含你有一种特殊的方式
package your application
打包您的应用程序
you know you now can run your
你知道你现在可以运行你的
application in all kinds of different
在各种不同的应用
application servers that's very good
非常好的应用服务器
very positive news for us we can move
对我们来说是非常积极的消息，我们可以搬家
application for one containing one
申请一个包含一个
application services and access that's
应用程序服务和访问
amazing works very well but how about
很棒的作品很好，但是怎么样
installation application server itself
安装应用程序服务器本身
you know if you want to move from you
你知道你是否想离开你
want to still use the same application
仍要使用相同的应用程序
server but you want to move from your
服务器，但您想从
laptop to the server in your company or
笔记本电脑连接到您公司的服务器或
you want to move to the server in your
您想移到您的服务器中
company to the cloud server why do you
公司到云服务器为什么你
do you have to reinstall the whole thing
你必须重新安装整个东西吗
again right you know you have to
再一次，你知道你必须
reinstall application server we have to
重新安装应用程序服务器，我们必须
reinstall all the dependency you have to
重新安装所有依赖项
restart up the operation system you have
重新启动您拥有的操作系​​统
to reconfigure everything
重新配置一切
not very portable isn't it's portable
不是很便携不是吗
between application servers but your
在应用程序服务器之间，但您的
whole setup it's not portable so if you
整个设置不是便携式的，所以如果您
want to use application server in a good
想要很好地使用应用服务器
way
方式
how about if you package the application
如果打包应用程序怎么样
server inside a container that's what
容器内的服务器就是
doctors for right we can package the
医生的权利，我们可以打包
whole application server inside another
整个应用服务器位于另一个内部
container a docker container uh I gotta
集装箱一个码头集装箱我要
there's a cool tweet the other day and a
前几天有一条很酷的推文，
guy saying my mom saw a doctor sticker
说我妈妈看过医生的家伙贴纸
my laptop and freak it out
我的笔记本电脑吓坏了
so docker is not blue whale okay all
所以码头工人不是蓝鲸好吗
right
对
if you don't know what I'm talking about
如果你不知道我在说什么
yeah forget it don't worry but um
是的，忘记它不用担心
docker is the packaging the biggest
码头工人是最大的包装
innovation of DOC brought to us is the
DOC创新给我们带来的是
packaging you know er Scott
包装你知道吗斯科特
well you know docker has no innovation
你知道码头工人没有创新
in docker he's telling me the other day
在码头工人，他有一天告诉我
you know it's all our Linux containers
你知道这就是我们所有的Linux容器
right LLS lcx right so how to say LCL
对吧，LSL lcx对，怎么说LCL
cgroups yeah let's just see groups right
cgroups是的，让我们看看正确的组
in in in in Linux containers right
在Linux容器中
Solaris zones yeah okay yeah I know so
是的，Solaris区域，是的，我知道
let's on is it a long time ago yes
让我们继续很久以前是的
both things are true the thing there is
这两件事都是真实的
not think the Oracle docker broth is not
不认为Oracle docker broth不是
the tools
工具
it's not easy commands the thing that
命令这不是一件容易的事
the doctor brought is the packaging now
医生带来的是现在的包装
you can easily package a container and
您可以轻松地包装容器并
everyone agrees that the package of
每个人都同意
docker is a good thing so when um when
码头工人是一件好事，所以当嗯
Amazon Oracle jelastic and all the
Amazon Oracle Jelastic和所有
providers adopt that same packaging it
提供者采用相同的包装
means that your container becomes
表示您的容器变成
portable between providers so that's a
在提供商之间可移植，因此这是一个
very very cool thing
非常非常酷的东西
um I don't we going to say something not
嗯，我不说些什么
now later all right so so docker is the
现在以后没事了，所以docker是
packaging of the container that you can
可以包装容器
use right so how does he does he work
使用权利，所以他如何工作
right so you know how to huh when you
对的，所以你知道怎么当你
packaged in a Java EE application you
打包在Java EE应用程序中
put inside Watts a year or a a war right
在瓦茨里面放一年或战争权利
a year or war depending on how complex
一年或战争取决于复杂程度
things you're doing so let's do a simple
您正在做的事情，让我们做一个简单的
one let's go
一走吧
that's my war right so I have my
那是我的战争权利，所以我有我的
applications or I'm just gonna put it
应用程序，否则我就放它
right here right so I have my lip my
就在这里，所以我有嘴唇
warm packaging I'm just going to pass it
温暖的包装，我要通过
as a parameter so I don't have to change
作为参数，所以我不必更改
my script every time I change my
每次更改我的脚本
application right I change change the
我更改申请权更改
name of application up so you can just
申请名称，以便您可以
pass your the name of your war as a
将您的战争名称作为
parameter so everything you do in Java
参数，因此您在Java中所做的一切
EE works nicely you know you've just
EE很不错，您知道您刚刚
spat your application you're fine you
吐出您的应用程序就可以了
can use maven someone to send means I'm
可以用某人发送Maven来表示我
using maven right you can use maybe we
使用Maven权利，你可以使用也许我们
should create your war file for example
例如应该创建您的战争文件
um so then I'm going to run a command
嗯，那么我要运行一个命令
docker build docker build builds a
docker build docker build构建一个
container see the packaging builds the
容器，请参见包装说明
packaging of the containers going to put
包装容器的放置
my application side the packaging and
我的应用程序在包装和
I'm going to give a name to it so I can
我要给它起个名字，这样我就可以
reference later ok so basically I'm here
稍后参考好吧，基本上我在这里
I'm creating a container so next thing I
我正在创建一个容器，所以接下来我
need to do is this you need anyone
需要做的是这你需要任何人
notice what changes here you're here
注意这里的变化
nothing change it yes it did this little
没什么改变是的
dot hinder ends right this is just
点障碍结束了，这只是
saying I want to build that container on
说我想建立那个容器
this direction right now and on this
现在和这个方向
reactor I have this file the docker file
我有这个文件docker文件
the docker file is the instructions on
docker文件是关于
how I build my container right so I know
我如何正确地建立容器，所以我知道
it has things like oh it starts from a
它有类似的东西，哦，它从一个开始
Tommy EE pre-existing image we're going
Tommy EE预先存在的图像，我们要去
to talk about this in a minute add some
一会儿再说这个
configuration for high availability add
高可用性配置
some configuration for users right so
给用户一些配置吧
I'm just kind of hard coding everything
我只是对所有内容进行硬编码
here just to make it easy so so again a
这里只是为了使它变得容易，所以再次
lot of things are hard-coded because you
很多事情都是硬编码的，因为您
can run this in your laptop right so you
可以在您的笔记本电脑上运行它，所以您
know you go you go to the article
知道你去，你去看这篇文章
there's a github account there you don't
那里有一个github帐户
work for the github you just run the
为github工作，您只需运行
whole thing in your laptop so we add
整个东西放在您的笔记本电脑中，因此我们添加
some configuration for data sources we
数据源的一些配置
add that driver for post grade so it can
将该驱动程序添加为后期成绩，以便可以
access poetry so you see in the
访问诗歌，以便您在
container I have everything I need to
容器我有我需要的一切
run my application right so I have all
正确运行我的应用程序，以便我拥有所有
the libraries I need I have all the
我需要的图书馆
configurations I need I have everything
我需要的配置我拥有一切
I need to run application inside the
我需要在
container and then the last thing here I
容器，然后是我的最后一件事
ads the war file and look I install the
广告war文件，然后看我安装了
war file in the web apps directory off
Web应用程序目录中的war文件关闭
Tommy for Tommy this means that I'm
Tommy for Tommy，这意味着我
stalling the update Java Java EE
停止更新Java Java EE
application if it was another
如果是另一个应用程序
application server you might have to do
您可能需要做的应用服务器
something different installed
安装了一些不同的东西
application but notice that my container
应用程序，但请注意我的容器
will have the application storage ready
将准备好应用程序存储
to run when you add your application to
在将应用程序添加到时运行
the container that's an image right
就是图像的容器
remember when you created visual images
记住当您创建视觉图像时
in the clouds that what you do you would
在云端，你会做什么
kind of create like a base image amazing
有点像基本图像一样的创造
stall and then every time you change
停顿，然后每次改变
application you just upload the war file
您只需上传战争文件的应用程序
to the to the to the to machine with
到到到机器
containers we could do this with virtual
容器，我们可以使用虚拟
machine - but if containers can do a
机器-但是如果容器可以
very cool thing that we can create
我们可以创造的非常酷的东西
appliances an appliance is a ready to
电器已经准备好
run image with everything that I need
用我需要的一切运行图像
prayer configured ready to run so I have
祈祷已准备就绪，可以运行了
the latest version of application right
最新版本的申请权
here install it ready to run what
在这里安装它准备运行什么
happens if I need to upgrade an
如果我需要升级
application I create a new version of
我创建了一个新版本的应用程序
the container it just just insert a new
容器，只需插入一个新的
version my container okay
版本我的容器好
so I'm going to do this really quick
所以我要很快做
then you know I'm going to start the
那你知道我要开始
container here doctor creates create
医生在这里创建的容器创建
create create and creating three
创建创建和创建三个
containers different ports right based
容器基于不同的端口
on the same image Tommy you are the same
在同一张图片上，汤米，你是同一个人
configuration I'm creating a cluster
配置我正在创建集群
here and then I'm going to add a load
在这里，然后我要添加一个负载
balancer this load balancer here is
这个负载均衡器是
another container I just download from
我刚刚从另一个容器下载
the internet I don't need to do anything
互联网我什么也不需要做
right now so you know I have some
现在，所以你知道我有一些
configurations for it but that's okay
的配置，但没关系
right so with this I have four machines
对，所以我有四台机器
a load balancer three application
一个负载均衡器的三个应用
servers running on a high availability
高可用性服务器
solution with four commands for my
我的四个命令的解决方案
computer that's it you can run your
就是这样，您可以运行您的计算机
laptop this the whole thing and of
笔记本电脑这整个事情和
course I'm doing here doctor creates so
我在这里做的当然是医生创造的
it just creates the containers when I I
它只是在创建容器时
can start it with docker starts or I can
可以用docker starts来启动它，或者我可以
do something easier I can just run two
做一些简单的事情，我可以只运行两个
commands in one I can just use docker
我可以只使用docker中的命令
run and I'm just going to run those
运行，我将运行那些
commands right there okay
命令就在那里
so with this four commands I have this
所以用这四个命令我有这个
whole environment I have a load balancer
整个环境我都有一个负载均衡器
three Tommy's servers up and running on
三个Tommy的服务器启动并运行
my laptop what did I do with this well
我的笔记本电脑我怎么做得好
you can get now the same the same four
你现在可以得到相同的四个
commands you can run in your test server
您可以在测试服务器中运行的命令
and you have your test environments the
并且您拥有测试环境
same four commands you can run your
您可以运行相同的四个命令
production servers now you have a
生产服务器，现在您有了
production environment the exact same
生产环境完全一样
containers you can run anywhere if
您可以在任何地方运行的容器
tomorrow you want to experiment with
明天你想尝试
jelastic right juh last right here you
jelastic right juh last right here you
can just run the same four commands on
可以只在上面运行相同的四个命令
July's platform and you have your pure
七月的平台，您可以尽情享受
your your containers running the cloud
您的容器正在运行云
if you want to do Oracle you can do the
如果您想使用Oracle，可以执行
same thing right
没错
can just run the four commands on an
可以只在一个
Oracle machine in Oracle clouds and
Oracle云中的Oracle机器和
you're going to have all this
你将拥有所有这一切
environment running on another provider
在另一个提供程序上运行的环境
right so very easy for you to migrate
对，所以您很容易迁移
things from one place to the next
事情从一个地方到另一个地方
it's very easy for you to test your
您可以很容易地测试您的
environments no no no more those things
环境没有，没有更多的东西
all you know I might test environments
知道我可能会测试环境
completely run production environment
完全运行生产环境
because they are different things with
因为他们与
containers you have very similar
你有非常相似的容器
environments both sides and the
双方的环境
interesting thing is that a docker
有趣的是，一个码头工人
allows us to do something more
让我们做更多的事情
interesting there is there is a load of
有趣的是有一个负载
pre-existing containers in the internet
互联网中预先存在的容器
they can just download and use it
他们可以下载并使用它
immediately
立即
right so for example you know all these
对，例如，您知道所有这些
sea of containers if there's a huge
如果有巨大的集装箱海
repository of containers with lots and
有很多容器的仓库
lots and lots of pre-existing containers
很多很多预先存在的容器
and I can just go and say oh let me let
我可以说哦，让我让
me find a tommy server and I also need a
我找到了一个汤米服务器，我还需要一个
poster database I also need a active any
海报数据库我也需要一个主动的
kill a message servicing I just kind of
杀死消息服务我只是
use them and I also need Cassandra
用它们，我也需要Cassandra
service you know toggles right there and
您知道的服务就在那里切换
so we can use Cassandra and I can just
所以我们可以使用Cassandra，我可以
like connect my Tomy server to all of
就像将我的Tomy服务器连接到所有
those guys and I have a very
那些家伙，我有一个非常
sophisticated environment I can just add
我可以添加的复杂环境
a load balance on top of this and now I
最重要的是负载平衡，现在我
have a sophisticated architecture it out
具有复杂的架构
configuring anything just reusing
配置任何东西只是重复使用
existing come
存在来
Rainer's there you can download from the
您可以从此处下载Rainer
internet and actually don't even need to
上网，实际上甚至不需要
download them just by passing doc to
只需将文档传递到
doctor a name of the thing you're using
为您使用的事物命名
doc you automatically download install
您自动下载安装文档
locally and run for you right so it's a
在本地为您运行，这是一个
lot easier for you to build a very
您轻松建立一个非常
sophisticated architecture a lot easy
复杂的架构非常容易
for you to automate your own work you
为您实现自己的工作自动化
know remember when you said this a lot
知道记得你说过很多话
of people don't automate their own work
的人没有使自己的工作自动化
a lot easier first you automate our own
首先让您自动化我们自己要容易得多
work alright so the cool thing I've
工作正常，所以我很酷
mentioned this a few times but all of
提到了几次，但所有
those providers here know including
这些供应商知道
Oracle and jelastic the two the two guys
甲骨文和杰弹性两个人
are sponsoring us here in our tour those
在我们的巡回演出中赞助我们
guys here all of them they run
大家在这里他们都跑
containers they all understand doctor
他们都了解医生的容器
containers they all run docker
他们都运行docker的容器
containers so you can actually have all
容器，因此您实际上可以拥有所有
of the stuff running on any provider and
在任何提供程序上运行的东西
the cool thing is you know this
很酷的事情是你知道这个
particular thing that we can do right
我们可以做的特别的事情
now so from all of those providers here
现在所有这些提供者都在这里
jelastic is they've been doing
jelastic他们一直在做
containers for for longer than most and
容器的使用寿命比大多数
one cool thing that we can do in those
我们可以在这些方面做的一件很酷的事情
guys in all of them we do eventually is
大家我们最终要做的是
that we can actually migrate from cloud
我们实际上可以从云迁移
vendors right today we're going to do
我们今天要做的供应商
this after we finish the tour we're
完成巡回演出后，
going to host a series of webinars
将举办一系列的网络研讨会
online they were going to invite people
他们将在网上邀请人们
that could not come here to the tour to
那不可能来这里参观
come talk to you guys about cool things
来和你们聊聊有趣的事情
so we're going to do a demo of running a
因此，我们将进行运行
container running a positive that that's
容器运行一个积极的
minecraft run a minecraft server and
我的世界运行一个我的世界服务器
we're going to migrate the container for
我们将要迁移容器
minecraft from one cloud provider to
我的世界从一个云提供商
another cloud provider it doubt downtime
另一家云提供商怀疑停机时间
you you're going to be playing you can
你将要玩，你可以
do this you can be in your computer
做到这一点，你可以在你的电脑上
playing Minecraft with us and we're
和我们一起玩《我的世界》，我们
going to migrate the server from one
要从一个迁移服务器
clouds to another cloud and you're just
云到另一云，你就是
going to continue to play right through
将继续玩下去
it we can do this today he's like oh man
今天我们可以做到这一点，他就像哦，男人
that's not possible what you want to do
那是不可能的，你想做什么
it yes but you thought you think that's
是的，但是你以为那是
not possible no you think that's
不可能，不，你认为那是
possible right yes it's possible
可能是的，可能
right containers allow us to package
合适的容器可以包装
things in a way that we can we have the
以我们可以拥有的方式
tools today
今天的工具
to do this kind of things right that in
正确地做这种事情
the past could sound like crazy but now
过去听起来很疯狂，但现在
we can actually have multiple cloud
我们实际上可以有多个云
providers guaranteeing high availability
提供者保证高可用性
between providers and even live
提供者之间，甚至生活之间
migration off containers to different
从容器迁移到其他
provides so we're going to do all those
提供，所以我们将要做所有这些
kind of things right so Brian don't come
有些事情是对的，所以布莱恩不要来
here with me and say in how about you
跟我在这里说你呢
connect your computer and then we can do
连接您的计算机，然后我们可以做
we can do those two things you want me
我们可以做你想要我的两件事
to do my first and you do for now you do
首先要做我，现在做
your first and then all right it's your
首先，然后是您的
first right so containers really allow
首先正确，所以容器确实允许
us to do some very sophisticated things
我们做一些非常复杂的事情
and that's that's it it's extremely
那就是它的极端
important that you learn how to do
学习如何做很重要
containers now right because the sooner
容器现在正确，因为更快
you learn how to do containers you know
你学习如何做你知道的容器
all those guys will raise their hand say
所有这些家伙都会举手说
I'm looking for a job right the sooner
我要早点找工作
you know that stuff the sooner you plain
你知道那东西越早你就明白了
within your laptop you know you know how
在笔记本电脑中，您知道您知道如何
things was in the past yeah okay not the
事情是过去的，是的，不是
past was like when I when I was the age
过去就像我那年纪的时候
of you guys especially I'm you know you
你们当中的一些人，尤其是我，你认识你
think you're doing this yeah I'm just
认为你正在这样做，是的，我只是
gonna pick on you right now right so you
现在要接你，所以你
know when I was your age I was I would
知道我几岁的时候我会
see those vendors coming in and you'd
看到那些供应商进来，你会
say oh you know you can use this this
说哦，你知道你可以用这个
very sophisticated piece of software
非常复杂的软件
here is this object-oriented application
这是这个面向对象的应用程序
server as it exists something like this
服务器，因为它存在这样的东西
right and very cool ah
对，很酷啊
and then you say ho in it how can I do
然后你说在里面怎么办
this well it costs $30,000 a license per
每口许可证的费用为30,000美元
developer and so I would I would sing
开发人员，所以我会唱歌
down my chairs like okay I'm never going
好吧，我永远都不会去
to learn this you know I need to work
要学习这个，你知道我需要工作
for a company that's willing to pay a
对于愿意支付一定费用的公司
product it cost $30,000 for me to play
产品花了我30,000美元玩
with it I'm not going to have that the
有了它，我就不会拥有
cool thing about today is everything
今天最酷的事情就是一切
we're talking here you know from what
我们在这里说话，你知道什么
Ian said what otago said what I said all
伊恩（Ian）说了什么
of those things are completely free and
这些东西是完全免费的，
available for you right now
现在为您提供
right so you can right now from your
对的，所以您现在就可以从
laptop just do all these
笔记本电脑可以完成所有这些工作
you
您